

Contact

Phone

+375333518629

Email

nikita.pohods@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikita-pohodski/

Github

https://github.com/nikita-pohodski

Location

Minsk

Education

2020

Java developer

IT Academy

2016

Automation of technological processes and production

BGKPSM branch of BNTU

Skills

Java, TypeScript, JavaScript Spring (Boot, Security, Cloud) Node.js, Nest.js, Express.js MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB Hibernate, Prisma, Sequelize Redis, RabbitMQ, Kafka Keycloak AWS. GCP **Firebase**

Swagger (include codegen)

Ether.js

React.js, Vue.js v2, Electron

Twilio

Docker

Languages

Russian **English**

Mikita Pahodski

Backend Developer

Experience

2023 - 2024

MKNL Technology LTD

Backend developer

Participated in the development of the AnyCall platform, which provides the ability to make calls between various platforms (GSM, VoIP, landline phones). Specifically, I developed a microservice for working with virtual numbers using Node.js, Sequelize, RabbitMQ, and Redis technologies. Additionally, I contributed to the creation of a desktop application for translating messages in a messenger using Electron.

Technologies: Node.js, Express.js ,Nest.js, Sequelize, RabbitMQ, Redis, Microservices

2022 - 2023

AliumSwap/MMgraph

Backend developer

Maintained an existing market-making solution for centralized exchanges (CEX). Developed an application and an administration panel for market-making on decentralized exchanges (DEX). Also developed an arbitrage bot for trading pairs on DEX.

Technologies: Node.js, Nest.js, Refine, Ethers.js.

2021 - 2022

AWTG Ltd

Backend developer

While working on the company's local project, I improved code quality and created reusable components. During this time, I grew to a mid-level developer as I completed tasks without the help of a team lead.

Working on a project for a volunteer organization in Ireland, I mastered new technologies. I used Node.js (Nest.js) and maintained microservices written in Java (Spring).

Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Keycloak, WebSocket, Node.js, TypeScript, Nest.js, Prisma ORM, Swagger (including Swagger Codegen for generating API clients), PostgreSQL, MongoDB, GCP.

0 2020 - 2021

Real Technologies

Java Developer

I worked as a Full Stack developer on a fintech project. I developed most of the backend for the mobile application and the admin panel (Java, Spring Boot), as well as most of the frontend for the admin panel (Vue.js).

Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Minio, Vue.js, Docker, AWS.

About

Personal: I love music, outdoor activities, and intellectual games.

Professional: Throughout my work experience, I have been the "architect" of four services, taking them from inception to production. I quickly find solutions for complex problems and have a strong understanding of business requirements.